Orb
محجر العين
I'm back
لقد عدت
Who allowed you to come back
من سمح لك بالعودة
Your birthday is coming up
عيد ميلادك قادم
I haven't even spent your birthday with you yet
أنا لم أقضي عيد ميلادك معك بعد
Of course I'm coming back
بالطبع سأعود
What about the gifts
ماذا عن الهدايا
I am the gift
أنا الهدية
Orb
محجر العين
Don't talk
لا تتحدث
What are you doing
ماذا تفعل
Your punishment
عقابك
Can't you
لا تستطيع
Of course
بالطبع
You can punish it as long as you want
يمكنك معاقبته طالما تريد
Father
أب
Who the hell are you bringing me to see
من بحق الجحيم أنت تحضرني لأرى
You'll know when you get there
ستعرف عندما تصل إلى هناك
There's a toad. Help
هناك الضفدع.  يساعد
There are toads
هناك الضفادع
Save me
انقذني
Guards save me
الحراس ينقذوني
There are toads there
هناك الضفادع هناك
Prince Ben is wandering around the royal courtyard
الأمير بن يتجول في الفناء الملكي
Want to pick a bunch of flowers for the princess
تريد اختيار مجموعة من الزهور للأميرة
Unexpectedly, I was disturbed by the toad
بشكل غير متوقع، لقد انزعجت من الضفدع
That's enough
هذا يكفي
Orb
محجر العين
This is from China this summer
هذا من الصين هذا الصيف
Prince Adafan
الأمير عدوان
Know that your birthday is near
اعلم أن عيد ميلادك قريب
I have come to congratulate you
لقد جئت لتهنئتك
Right, right, right
صحيح، صحيح، صحيح
Prince Adafan
الأمير عدوان
I personally came to Weidu to present a gift this time
لقد أتيت شخصيًا إلى Weidu لتقديم هدية هذه المرة
It's really sincere
انها حقا صادقة
I hope our two countries
وآمل أن بلدينا
In the future, we can turn war into friendship
في المستقبل، يمكننا تحويل الحرب إلى صداقة
Where are the gifts
أين الهدايا
It's far away, just around the corner
إنه بعيد، قاب قوسين أو أدنى
That's me
هذا أنا
What treasure
ما الكنز
It can represent the sincerity of good relations between the two countries
يمكن أن يمثل صدق العلاقات الجيدة بين البلدين
I'm the only priceless treasure
أنا الكنز الوحيد الذي لا يقدر بثمن
I see
أرى
Is it a clown
هل هو مهرج
Come here this time
تعال هنا هذه المرة
I also brought the Imperial Medical Garden
أحضرت أيضًا الحديقة الطبية الإمبراطورية
A prescription developed for many years
وصفة طبية تم تطويرها لسنوات عديدة
Can solve the cold poison of Princess Baozhu
يمكن أن يحل السم البارد للأميرة باوزو
This summer, Ming Jun is in power
هذا الصيف، مينغ جون في السلطة
It's a blessing
انها نعمة
It's just
انه فقط
I don't know the prescription that can solve the cold poison of Baozhu
لا أعرف الوصفة الطبية التي يمكنها حل سم باوزهو البارد
Where now
اين الان
This is the father
هذا هو الأب
The reason why I was sent here this time
سبب إرسالي إلى هنا هذه المرة
If your majesty will betroth the princess to me
إذا كان جلالتك سيخطب لي الأميرة
Make the two countries good
جعل البلدين على خير
The prescription should be given with both hands
وينبغي إعطاء الوصفة الطبية بكلتا اليدين
I don't know Prince Adavan
أنا لا أعرف الأمير أدافان
Which princess do you want to marry
من هي الأميرة التي تريد الزواج منها؟
Instead of letting my father and Jin Jiu
بدلاً من السماح لوالدي وجين جيو
Sad for my body
حزين على جسدي
It's better to take this opportunity
فمن الأفضل أن أغتنم هذه الفرصة
Escape from Weidu Country
الهروب من بلد Weidu
Father
أب
My daughter wants to visit China this summer
ابنتي تريد زيارة الصين هذا الصيف
Orb
محجر العين
I don't know Prince Adavan
أنا لا أعرف الأمير أدافان
Would you like to be a guide
هل ترغب في أن تكون دليلا
This must be Princess Baozhu
يجب أن تكون هذه الأميرة باوزو
If the princess is interested, Adafan can't ask for it
إذا كانت الأميرة مهتمة، فلا يستطيع أدافان أن يطلب ذلك
Baozhu can't fool around
لا يستطيع Baozhu العبث
What we are discussing now
ما نناقشه الآن
But marital events
لكن الأحداث الزوجية
I
أنا
I also have a way to detoxify
لدي أيضًا طريقة لإزالة السموم
If you want to marry a princess,
إذا كنت تريد الزواج من أميرة،
Is to relieve cold toxin
هو لتخفيف سموم البرد
I hope your majesty will give me a chance
آمل أن يمنحني جلالتك فرصة
Mrs. Prison
سجن السيدة
Guard
يحمي
All right
حسنًا
Jin Jiu is the bodyguard chosen by Baozhu
Jin Jiu هو الحارس الشخصي الذي اختاره Baozhu
Prince Adafan
الأمير عدوان
Don't speculate at random
لا تتكهن بشكل عشوائي
I'm afraid it will damage the friendship between the two countries
وأخشى أن ذلك سيضر بالصداقة بين البلدين
The marriage between the two countries
الزواج بين البلدين
I hope your majesty will consider it carefully
آمل أن يفكر جلالتك في الأمر بعناية
It's about Baozhu's life
إنها تدور حول حياة باوزهو
I hope your majesty will think twice
آمل أن يفكر جلالتك مرتين
Three days later
بعد ثلاثة ايام
Birthday of the orb
عيد ميلاد الجرم السماوي
It was also the time when her cold poison broke out
وكان ذلك أيضًا هو الوقت الذي اندلع فيه سمها البارد
Who can relieve her of the cold poison
من يستطيع أن يريحها من السم البارد
Who is entitled to marry a princess
من يحق له الزواج من أميرة
A good dog is out of the way
كلب جيد هو خارج الطريق
You're in debt again, aren't you
أنت مدين مرة أخرى، أليس كذلك
This summer specialty I brought to the princess
هذا الصيف التخصصي الذي أحضرته للأميرة
For the safety of the princess
من أجل سلامة الأميرة
Something sent from outside
شيء مرسل من الخارج
I have to try poison
لا بد لي من تجربة السم
You
أنت
Things are dirty
الأمور قذرة
Would you please prepare another one
هل من الممكن أن تقوم بإعداد واحدة أخرى
You, you bully you too much
أنت، أنت تتنمر عليك كثيرًا
I'm telling you
أنا أخبرك
There's nobody now. I'm not afraid of you
لا يوجد أحد الآن.  أنا لست خائفا منك
Come with us
تعال معنا
Princess Baozhu Princess
الأميرة باوزهو الأميرة
Adafan came to visit Princess Baozhu
جاء أدافان لزيارة الأميرة باوزهو
Princess, you woke up
أيتها الأميرة، لقد استيقظت
Be honest
كن صادقا
Do you two know who I am
هل تعرفان من أنا
Be careful. I'll tell you later, the emperor
احرص.  سأخبرك لاحقًا أيها الإمبراطور
Kill you
أقتلك
You, you
أنت، أنت
Childe
تشايلد
What are you doing here
ما الذي تفعله هنا
Oh, my God
يا إلهي
Is this a fairy
هل هذه خرافية
Waste wood
نفايات الخشب
Because you want to marry my sister, too
لأنك تريد الزواج من أختي أيضاً
You said
أنت قلت
Is the moon this summer so round
هل القمر هذا الصيف مستدير جدًا؟
Do you have to go
هل عليك أن تذهب
Competition in three days
المنافسة في ثلاثة أيام
I don't want you to attend
لا أريدك أن تحضر
Why
لماذا
Don't you tell me
لا تخبرني
You want to marry that Prince Ada
تريد الزواج من ذلك الأمير آدا
You can't poison me
لا يمكنك أن تسممني
But I hope you can live to be seven or eighty
لكني آمل أن تتمكن من العيش حتى السابعة أو الثمانين
By the way, keep my share alive
بالمناسبة، حافظ على حصتي حية
To live to be twenty is a lifetime
أن تعيش حتى العشرين هو عمر كامل
Living to be eighty is also a lifetime
إن العيش حتى الثمانين هو أيضًا عمر كامل
As long as I can be with you
طالما أستطيع أن أكون معك
One second at a time
ثانية واحدة في كل مرة
It's all a lifetime
كل ذلك مدى الحياة
If you insist on marrying until this summer
إذا كنت مصرا على الزواج حتى هذا الصيف
Even if I do a dowry
حتى لو قمت بالمهر
I'll follow you for the rest of my life
سأتبعك لبقية حياتي
Adafan, you did a good job
أدافان، لقد قمت بعمل جيد
If you want to marry Baozhu,
إذا كنت تريد الزواج من باوزهو،
I have nothing to say
ليس لدي ما أقوله
Your Majesty can't
جلالتك لا تستطيع
Your Majesty
صاحب الجلالة
Actually, what I want to marry is
في الواقع، ما أريد أن أتزوجه هو
Princess
أميرة